Guide to the AFL-CIO Region 9 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- AFL-CIO Montana Materials, 1963-1996; SERIES III (Box-folder 5/1-10/53)
  - Montana State Federation of Labor, 1963-1996; Subseries A (Box-folder 5/1-9/30)
    - Part 8: Subject Files, 1963-1995 (Box-folder 8/3-9/30)
      - Montana State Article XX, 1991 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Montana State Establishment of Northeast Montana Central Labor Council, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Montana State Establishment of South Central Montana Central Labor Council, 1971-1992 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Montana State Poll and Building Trades Council, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Montana State Property Tax, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Montana State Business Trust, 1990 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Montana State Poll and Building Trades Council Letter, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Montana State Volunteers, 1989 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Montana State Heavy and Highway Construction Committee, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Montana State Job Opportunity and Business Stability, 1988 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Montana State "The Case Against a Federal Constitutional Convention", c.1980s (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Montana State Media Workshop Participants, 1989 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Montana State Missoula Central Labor Council Meeting 1990 October 11 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Montana State Helena Trades and Labor Council Meeting, 1963-1990 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Montana State Helena Trades and Labor Council Correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Montana State Establishment of Eastern Montana Central Labor Council, 1990 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Montana State Calls, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Montana State New Directions Conference, 1989 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Montana State Corporation for Enterprise Development (CFED), 1990 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Montana State Economic Development Seminar, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Montana State Associate Membership Program, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Montana State Montana Public Employees Association - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees - Service Employees International Union, 1990 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Montana State General Central Labor Councils, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Montana State Proposed Central Labor Councils, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Montana State Mailing Lists, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - Montana State Affiliation Program, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - Montana State Mailing Lists, 1991 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Montana State Building and Construction Trades Council Meeting, 1993 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Montana State Job Search Curriculum and Information Manual, Undated (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Montana Family Union Strategy Report, c. 1990s (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Montana Unions Not Affiliated with State Federation, 1990 (Box-folder 9/23)
      - Montana State Central Labor Councils General Information, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 9/24)
      - Montana Statewide Locals, 1990 (Box-folder 9/25)
      - Montana State Membership Per Capita, 1988 (Box-folder 9/26)
      - Montana State Murry Appreciation Dinner, 1991 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - Montana State Communication Workers of America #7640 Court Case, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 9/28)
      - Montana State Illegal Expenditure of Campaign Funds 1988 Election, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 9/29)
      - Montana State Computer Network, 1990 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Montana Local Labor Councils, 1971-1995; Subseries B (Box-folder 10/1-53)
    - Southwestern Montana Central Labor Council, 1987-1995; Sub-Subseries 1 (Box-folder 10/1-3)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1992 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - Flathead County Central Trades and Labor Council, 1987-1993; Sub-Subseries 2 (Box-folder 10/4-9)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1989 (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Part 5: Subject Files, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 10/8-9)
        - Flathead County Central Trades and Labor Council, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 10/8)
        - New Flathead Area Central Labor Council, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Eastern Montana Trades and Labor, 1977-1993; Sub-Subseries 3 (Box-folder 10/10-12)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Southeastern Montana Central Labor Council, 1990-1993; Sub-Subseries 4 (Box-folder 10/13-15)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - South Central Montana Central Labor Council, 1990-1994; Sub-Subseries 5 (Box-folder 10/16-18)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1992 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1992 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Northwest Montana Central Labor Council, 1990-1993; Sub-Subseries 6 (Box-folder 10/19-20)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Part 2: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Northeast Montana Central Labor Council, 1990-1993; Sub-Subseries 7 (Box-folder 10/21-23)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - North Central Montana Central Labor Council, 1990-1993; Sub-Subseries 8 (Box-folder 10/24-25)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - Part 2: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Missoula County Trades and Labor Councils, 1974-1992; Sub-Subseries 9 (Box-folder 10/26-32)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1992 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 10/27)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 10/28)
      - Part 4: Minutes, 1989 (Box-folder 10/29)
      - Part 5: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 10/30)
      - Part 6: Subject Files, 1974-1990 (Box-folder 10/31-32)
        - Missoula Area Trades and Labor Council, 1974-1989 (Box-folder 10/31)
        - Missoula County Trades and Labor Council, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Greater Yellowstone Central Labor Council, 1973-1994; Sub-Subseries 10 (Box-folder 10/33-35)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1973-1992 (Box-folder 10/33)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/34)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 10/35)
    - Big Sky Central Labor Council, 1990-1993; Sub-Subseries 11 (Box-folder 10/36-38)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/36)
      - Part 2: Executive Board Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/37)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Central Montana Central Labor Council, 1990-1994; Sub-Subseries 12 (Box-folder 10/39-40)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 10/39)
      - Part 2: Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 10/40)
    - Bozeman Central Labor Council, 1989-1990; Sub-Subseries 13 (Box-folder 10/41)
    - Cascade Central Labor Council, 1989-1990; Sub-Subseries 14 (Box-folder 10/42)
    - Eastern Montana Central Labor Council, 1977-1990; Sub-Subseries 15 (Box-folder 10/43)
    - Havre Trades and Labor Assembly, 1989-1990; Sub-Subseries 16 (Box-folder 10/44)
    - Helena Trades and Labor Council, 1989-1990; Sub-Subseries 17 (Box-folder 10/45)
    - Lincoln County Trades and Labor Council, 1989-1990; Sub-Subseries 18 (Box-folder 10/46)
    - Park Central Labor Council, 1989; Sub-Subseries 19 (Box-folder 10/47)
    - Silver Bow Trades and Labor Council, 1971-1991; Sub-Subseries 20 (Box-folder 10/48)
    - Yellowstone Valley Central Labor Council, 1973-1990; Sub-Subseries 21 (Box-folder 10/49)
    - Anaconda Central Labor Council, 1986-1991; Sub-Subseries 22 (Box-folder 10/50-53)
      - Yearly Reports, 1987-1990; Sub-Subseries 22, Part 1 (Box-folder 10/50)
      - Officers Election Reports, 1989; Sub-Subseries 22, Part 2 (Box-folder 10/51)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1991; Sub-Subseries 22, Part 3 (Box-folder 10/52)
      - Subject Files, 1989-1990; Sub-Subseries 22, Part 4 (Box-folder 10/53)
- AFL-CIO OREGON MATERIALS, 1966-1996; SERIES IV (Box-folder 11/1-12/51)
  - Oregon State Labor Council, 1966-1996; Subseries A (Box-folder 11/1-11/30)
    - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1966-1996 (Box-folder 11/1-4)
      - Oregon State Constitution and Bylaws Amendments, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Oregon State Constitution and Bylaws Amendments, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Oregon State Constitution and Bylaws Amendments, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Oregon State Constitution and Bylaws Including Committee on Political Education, 1966-1982 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 11/5-7)
      - Oregon State Yearly Reports, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Oregon State Yearly Reports, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 11/6)
      - Oregon State Officers Election Reports, 1987 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Part 3: Executive Board Meetings, c. 1980s-1992 (Box-folder 11/8-9)
      - Oregon State Executive Board, c. 1980s (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Oregon State Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Part 4: Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 11/10-15)
      - Oregon State Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - Oregon State Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Oregon State Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Oregon State Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 11/13)
      - Oregon State Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 11/14)
      - Oregon State Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Part 5: Conventions, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 11/16-18)
      - Oregon State Annual Convention Portland 1991 September 23-25 (Box-folder 11/16)
      - Oregon State Industrial Union Council Convention, 1991 (Box-folder 11/17)
      - Oregon State Annual Convention Portland 1993 September 26-29, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Part 6: Committee on Political Education, 1988-1995 (Box-folder 11/19-22)
      - Oregon State Biennial Committee on Political Education Conference 1994, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 11/19)
      - Oregon State Committee of Political Education, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 11/20)
      - Oregon State Legislative Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 11/21)
      - Oregon State Legislative Newsletter, 1995 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - Part 7: Community Services, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 11/23-25)
      - Oregon State Labor's Community Service Agency, 1980 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - Oregon State Community Services Agencies, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Oregon State Local Community Services Agencies, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 11/25)
    - Part 8: Subject Files, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 11/26-30)
      - Oregon State Central Labor Councils, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 11/26)
      - Oregon State Committee on the Future, 1994 (Box-folder 11/27)
      - Oregon State Resolutions, 1994 (Box-folder 11/28)
      - Oregon State Organizing Committee, c. 1980s (Box-folder 11/29)
      - Oregon State Absentee Ballot Program, 1988 (Box-folder 11/30)
  - Oregon Local Labor Councils, 1974-1995; Subseries B (Box-folder 12/1-51)
    - Central Oregon Labor Council, 1975-1993; Sub-Subseries 1 (Box-folder 12/1-12/4)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1981 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1975 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Clatsop County Central Labor Council, 1977-1995; Sub-Subseries 2 (Box-folder 12/5-8)
      - Part 1; Constitution and Bylaws, 1977 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1977-1995 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1975-1994 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Douglas County Central Labor Council, 1975-1993; Sub-Subseries 3 (Box-folder 12/9-11)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Part 2: Officers Election Reports, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Eastern Oregon Central Labor Council, 1975-1993; Sub-Subseries 4 (Box-folder 12/12-13)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Part 2: Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Lane County Central Labor Council, 1980-1994; Sub-Subseries 5 (Box-folder 12/14-17)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1989 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1980-1994 (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council, 1978-1994; Sub-Subseries 6 (Box-folder 12/18-26)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 12/18-19)
        - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council Constitution and Bylaws, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 12/18)
        - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council Amendments to Constitution, 1987 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1987 (Box-folder 12/21)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1978-1994 (Box-folder 12/22-24)
        - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 12/22)
        - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 12/23)
        - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council Correspondence, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Part 5: Subject Files, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 12/25-26)
        - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council Election 1985 June 24 (Box-folder 12/25)
        - Northwest Oregon Central Labor Council Local Union Training 1990 April 10-11 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Marion-Polk-Yamhill Central Labor Council, 1975-1992; Sub-Subseries 7 (Box-folder 12/27-30)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1990 (Box-folder 12/27)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 12/28)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 12/29)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 12/30)
    - Mid-Columbia Central Labor Council, 1975-1992; Sub-Subseries 8 (Box-folder 12/31-34)
      - Part 1: Constitution and Bylaws, 1977 (Box-folder 12/31)
      - Part 2: Yearly Reports, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Part 3: Officers Election Reports, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 12/33)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 12/34)
    - Linn-Benton-Lincoln County Central Labor Council, 1975-1992; Sub-Subseries 9 (Box-folder 12/35-37)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 12/35)
      - Part 2: Officers Election Reports, 1975-1990 (Box-folder 12/36)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 12/37)
    - Southwestern Oregon Central Labor Council, 1977-1993; Sub-Subseries 10 (Box-folder 12/38-41)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 12/38)
      - Part 2: Officers Election Reports, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 12/39)
      - Part 3: Executive Board Meetings, 1993 (Box-folder 12/40)
      - Part 4: Correspondence, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 12/41)
    - Umatilla Morrow Central Labor Council, 1977-1993; Sub-Subseries 11 (Box-folder 12/42-44)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 12/42)
      - Part 2: Officers Election Reports, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 12/43)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 12/44)
    - Southern Oregon Central Labor Council, 1975-1993; Sub-Subseries 12 (Box-folder 12/45-47)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 12/45)
      - Part 2: Officers Election Reports, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 12/46)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 12/47)
    - Multnomah County Central Labor Council, 1974-1986; Sub-Subseries 13 (Box-folder 12/48)
    - Southeastern Oregon Central Labor Council, 1975-1994; Sub-Subseries 14 (Box-folder 12/49-51)
      - Part 1: Yearly Reports, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 12/49)
      - Part 2: Officers Election Reports, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 12/50)
      - Part 3: Correspondence, 1975-1994 (Box-folder 12/51)
- AFL-CIO WASHINGTON MATERIALS, 1949-1978; SERIES V (Box-folder 13/1-14/16)
  - Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1949-1978; Subseries A (Box-folder 13/1-16)
    - Part 1: Correspondence, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 13/1-3)
      - Washington State Labor Council, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Washington State Correspondence Ken Bowman, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Washington State Communications to Central Bodies from Region and AFL-CIO, 1966-1978 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Part 2: Committee on Political Education, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Washington State Labor Council Legislative Reports, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Part 3: Washington State Labor-Management and Pension Plans Disclosure Reports, 1949-1978 (Box-folder 13/5-16)
      - Washington State Labor-Management and Pension Plans Disclosure Reports, 1954-1976 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Washington State Speakers Bureau, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries, 1949-1976 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Washington State Building and Construction Trades Council, 1978 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Washington State Legislative Information State and National, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Washington State Allstate Leasing Corporation, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Washington State Labor Council Reporting Forms, 1974-1974 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Washington State Labor Council Affiliation Figures, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Washington State Central Labor Council Fact Sheets, 1974-1974 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Northwest Lumber Inspectors' Union Number 20877, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Northwest Lumber Inspectors' Union Number 20877, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - Northwest Lumber Inspectors' Union Number 20877, 1958-1978 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Washington Local Labor Councils, 1955-1978; Subseries B (Box-folder 13/17-4/16)
    - Wenatchee Central Labor Council, 1957-1978; Sub-Subseries 1 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Cowlitz-Wahkiakum Counties Central Labor Council, 1966-1978; Sub-Subseries 2 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - East Jefferson County Central Labor Council, 1957-1969; Sub-Subseries 3 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Grays Harbor Central Labor Council, 1975-1978; Sub-Subseries 4 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - King County Central Labor Council, 1959-1978; Sub-Subseries 5 (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Pacific County Central Labor Council, 1958-1978; Sub-Subseries 6 (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Moses Lake Central Labor Council, 1957-1978; Sub-Subseries 7 (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Pierce County Central Labor Council, 1957-1978; Sub-Subseries 8 (Box-folder 13/24)
    - Lewis County Central Labor Council, 1957-1975; Sub-Subseries 9 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Walla Walla Central Labor Council, 1974-1978; Sub-Subseries 10 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Yakima and East Klickitat Counties Central Labor Council, 1958-1978; Sub-Subseries 11 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Whatcom County Central Labor Council, 1974-1978; Sub-Subseries 12 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Kitsap County Central Labor Council, 1958-1978; Sub-Subseries 13 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Snohomish County Central Labor Council, 1955-1978; Sub-Subseries 14 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Port Angeles Central Labor Council, 1957-1978; Sub-Subseries 15 (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Mason County Central Labor Council, 1957-1977; Sub-Subseries 16 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Kittitas County Central Labor Council, 1963-1977; Sub-Subseries 17 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Spokane Central Labor Council, 1956-1978; Sub-Subseries 18 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Thurston County Central Labor Council, 1958-1978; Sub-Subseries 19 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Skagit County Central Labor Council, 1955-1978; Sub-Subseries 20; 3 photographs c. 1968: Photo #1 (pictured (l-r): Ione Thrash -State Office, Norman Strode - Barbers, Si Coe (?) - Laborers, Ed Jackson - Retail Clerks, Pat Finn - Meat Cutters; Photo #2 (pictured (l-r): Ben Pardo - Sergeant-at-arms, Bob Morse - Trustee, Pat Finn - Reading Clerk, Lavelle Mills - Trustee, Bob Tyler - Trustee, Mike Jensen - Sec. Treasury, Glen Jones - Vice President, Ed Locker - Trustee, Fred Trentman - President; Photo #3 (pictured (l-r): Bob Tyler - Trustee, Fred Trentman - President, Bill Erwin, Bob Morse - Trustee) (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Bremerton Metal Trades Council, 1962-1973; Sub-Subseries 21 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Benton-Franklin Counties Central Labor Council, 1955-1978; Sub-Subseries 22 (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Longview Kelso Building Trades Council, 1972; Sub-Subseries 23 (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Clark, Skamania, and West Klickitat Counties Central Labor Council, 1957-1978; Sub-Subseries 24 (Box-folder 14/16)
- AFL-CIO ARIZONA MATERIALS, 1980-1987; SERIES VI (Box-folder 14/17)
- AFL-CIO CALIFORNIA MATERIALS, 1980-1994; SERIES VII (Box-folder 14/18-19)
  - California State Central and Local Bodies, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - California State Central and Local Bodies, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 14/19)
- AFL-CIO COLORADO MATERIALS, 1968-1992; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 14/20)
- AFL-CIO CONNETICUT MATERIALS, 1967-1968; SERIES IX (Box-folder 14/21)
- AFL-CIO INDIANA MATERIALS, 1968; SERIES X (Box-folder 14/22)
- AFL-CIO MISSIOURI MATERIALS, 1954; SERIES XI (Box-folder 14/23)
- AFL-CIO NEBRASKA MATERIALS, 1987; SERIES XII (Box-folder 14/24)
- AFL-CIO NEVADA MATERIALS, 1982-1994; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 14/25)
- AFL-CIO WYOMING MATERIALS, 1983-1990; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 14/26)